<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Block Assessment Survey</string>

    <!-- LoginRegisterActivity -->
    <string name="register_heading">Welcome</string>
    <string name="login_heading">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="register_desc">Create an account to start rating your places.</string>
    <string name="login_desc">Log in to continue rating your places.</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Email Address</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="switch_text_login">Don\'t have an account? Register now ></string>
    <string name="switch_text_register">Already have an account? Log in ></string>
    <string name="register_success">Your account has successfully been registered. Logging you in…</string>
    <string name="register_failed">Your account was unable to be registered at this time. Please try again or log in if you already have an account.</string>
    <string name="login_success">You have been logged in successfully.</string>
    <string name="login_failed">Unable to log in. If you have not created an account, press the Register Now link to create an account.</string>
    <string name="email_password_req">Please enter both a username and password.</string>
    <string name="email_not_valid">The email you specified is not valid. Please enter a valid email address.</string>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="loc_enter_prompt">To review or view reviews for your neighborhood, enter its street address.
    \n\nTry pressing "Use My Current Location" below to fill in those fields automatically.</string>
    <string name="street_hint">Street Name</string>
    <string name="city_hint">City Name</string>
    <string name="use_curr_loc">Use My Current Location</string>
    <string name="loc_in_use">Using My Current Location - Press the button below to continue</string>
    <string name="loc_success">Location acquired! Press the \"See Reviews for Selected Location\" button to continue.</string>
    <string name="need_cur_loc">For the best experience, we will need your permission to access your current location. This is optional, used to autofill your street, city, and state for your assessment, and your exact location will not be stored.
    \n\nPress OK below and the permissions to continue, or deny the permissions and manually enter your street address.</string>
    <string name="loc_not_valid">This location is not valid. Please choose another.</string>
    <string name="loc_us_only">You can only review locations in the United States at the moment.</string>
    <string name="loc_empty">Please provide a street name, city name, and state to proceed.</string>
    <string name="loc_not_found">Unable to get your current location. Please enter it manually.</string>
    <string name="see_reviews">See Reviews For Selected Location!</string>

    <!-- ViewReviewsActivity -->
    <string name="view_reviews_title">Reviews</string>
    <string name="has_reviewed">You have already reviewed this location.</string>
    <string name="has_not_reviewed">You have not reviewed this location. Press the \"+\" button below to add a review.</string>
    <string name="review_fetch_failed">Unable to display reviews for this location. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="location_inval">This location is invalid. Please select a valid one.</string>
    <string name="view_comments_hint">View Comments</string>
    <string name="add_review_hint">Add Review</string>

    <!-- ReviewActivity -->
    <string name="review_title">New Review</string>
    <string name="new_review_desc">Rate on a scale of 1 to 5 (1 = strongly disagree, 5 = agree) how you feel about each of the below statements regarding the quality of your block.
    \n\nYou must rate at least one aspect, but you may leave some blank.
    \n\nYou may add additional details and comments in the \"Other Comments\" section below the ratings.
    \n\nOnce you submit your review, you will not be able to change it or review this block again.</string>
    <string name="comments_fld_heading">Other Comments</string>
    <string name="comments_fld_hint">Add specific feedback about any of the factors above.</string>
    <string name="review_submit">Submit Review</string>
    <string name="review_success">Your review has been posted!</string>
    <string name="review_error">Unable to post your review. Please try again.</string>

    <!-- CommentsActivity -->
    <string name="comments_title">Comments</string>
    <string name="no_comments_ind">No comments. You can add one by reviewing this block.</string>
    <string name="comments_fetch_failed">Unable to display comments for this location. Please try again later.</string>
</resources>